Guide to the Edward A. Feigenbaum Papers SC0340
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2005-101
  - United States Air Force
    - Talk--Department of Defense as a Japanese Company (EAF Talk), undated (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Visitors--Australian Delegation, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Communications with Boeing, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Infared Sensors, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Information Security Research Project--To Do, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - DARPA Materials, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - 2nd Intelligent Tutoring Systems Research Forum - proceedings, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Office of the Secretary of Defense Attendence Report for Consultants and Experts, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Institute for the Future--publications, 1996--1997 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Slides for New New World Vistas--IT talk, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Misc. ARPA / DARPA Papers, 1970--1980 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Critical Software Meeting (USAF, Japan Software Threat), 1990 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - DARPA Re: ISTO, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - ARPANET Directory: Defense Communications Agency, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - DARPA Advisory Board, Arlington, VA, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - USAF Scientific Adv. Bd.--Scott AFB, Illinois, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 68)
    - Pentagon Visit, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 72)
    - Horizons meeting, McLellan AFB, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 73)
    - SAB, Irvine, CA, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 75)
    - DARPA, Arlington, VA EMPTY, 1983 (Box 44)
    - DARPA, Expenses., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Principle Investigators--DARPA Contractors Meeting, Monterey, 1983 (Box 44, Folder 81)
    - ISAT / Washington DC, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - ISAT Washington Dc, 1992 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - ISAT Study, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - ISAT Los Angeles, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - DARPA Expert Systems, Palo Alto, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 52)
    - Tri-Service Artificial Intelligence (AI) Review (1/4), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Tri-Service Artificial Intelligence (AI) Review (2/4), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Tri-Service Artificial Intelligence (AI) Review (3/4), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Tri-Service Artificial Intelligence (AI) Review (4/4), 1986 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - DoD Artificial Intelligence (AI) Review--EAF's Notes on Tri-Service Review, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Invitation to join ISAT, 1988 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Box Notes and Talking Points Box 54, 2006 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - ISAT Binder, 1988 OCt (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - ISAT (1 of 2), 1988 Sep (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - ISAT (2 of 2), 1988 Sep (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - ISAT, 1989 Feb (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - ISAT Study Group, 1989--1990 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - ISAT--Alexandria, Va., 1990 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - ISAT (1 of 2), 1990 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - ISAT (2 of 2), 1990 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - ISAT, 1990-1991 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - ISAT Study Group, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - ISAT Wood's Hole, MA (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - ISAT Wood's Hole, MA (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - ISAT Study Group, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - DARPA--Strategic Computing, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Sea Dragon--Forward from the Sea (US DoD), undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Aerobureau, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Information Bomb, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Warrior Preperation Center Overview (US DoD), 1994; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - NIST Colloq. Series: "Software Development In the US and Japan" by EAF, Chief Scientest USAF, 1995; 1 videotape(s) (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Duplicating master, 1 computer file(s) (mov)
      - Use copy, 1995; 1 optical disc(s) (dvd) (Box 73, Folder 16.1)
    - CCLS "Bits and Piece: Bringing the Information Age to the US Air Force, 1998; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - USAF New World Vistas, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - War Breaker Simulation Program Zealous Pursuit, 1993; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Bioterrorism, undated; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - DARPA Strategic Cyber Defense, 1999; 1 videotape(s) (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Additional material, 1982-1983; Accession ARCH-2009-193
  - TEK Unified Contract, 1982-83 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - TEK--conflict of interest, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Ed Feigenbaum's Search for A.I." [video recording-streaming], 2006-2007; Accession ARCH-2010-108; 1 computer file(s) (flv)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
  Length: 45:51
  Flash Video format requires Flash Player available at: http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer.
  Scope and Contents note
  Acccessible at: https://lib.stanford.edu/search-for-ai-video
  This video production documents the life and career of Ed Feigenbaum, "Father of Expert Systems," through archival photographs, a Computer History Museum oral history (2007), and the recollections of his collaborators and students.
  Directed and edited by Ryan Cooper.
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2015-080
  - Trancripts of audio and video tapes (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Hard Drive: SALT Mac backup plus Feigenbaum video and audio files (Box 2)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-2016-046
  - Computer media, 17 optical disc(s) (Box 1)